http://www.pro-fusiononline.com/terms-conditions.html

Privacy Policy
Elderfield & Hall maintains the strongest possible privacy policy. When you place an order for a product, we will need to know your name, e-mail and mailing addresses, and your billing information so that we can fill, confirm and ship your order, and notify you of your order status. This site may collect your IP address or domain name for site administration purposes. We don't rent, sell or otherwise distribute to others any information about our customers, except that we may, and almost certainly will, provide your personal information to companies engaged to deliver your order. We also reserve the right to disclose without notice to you any information in our possession if we believe we are required to do so by law, to protect or defend our rights or property, or to respond to an emergency. While we endeavor to use reasonable efforts to safeguard the confidentiality of your information, the Internet is not totally secure. Due to the possibility of transmission errors, hacking or other unauthorized third party activities, we cannot guarantee that data on our site will remain secure. If we become aware of a security breach involving this website, Elderfield & Hall will make all legally required disclosures, consistent with our ability to determine the scope of the breach, our need to restore the integrity of the system and the needs of law enforcement. This site is not intended for use by, and Elderfield & Hall does not intend to collect personal information from, children under 13 years of age. Children under 13 years of age are directed not to use this site, whether to submit personal information or otherwise. Our website may contain links to websites which are not under the control of Elderfield & Hall. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of any linked site.
Shipping
Your purchase may be returned to us within 7 days of your receiving it, no questions asked. You must return it in the original packaging, and ship it insured at your expense for a full refund minus the original shipping charges.
Terms & Conditions
INTRODUCTION
ACCEPTANCE OF CONTRACT TERMS
By accessing this website and/or purchasing products from us, you agree that you have read, understood and agree to be bound by all of the provisions set forth herein and below (collectively, the "Terms and Conditions"), all of which constitute an agreement between you and Elderfield & Hall, Inc. The unenforceability of any one of the Terms and Conditions shall not affect the enforceability of any of the other Terms and Conditions. The terms and conditions on any quotation, order acknowledgment, invoice or other form you receive from Elderfield & Hall are incorporated into these Terms and Conditions by reference. These Terms and Conditions constitute the exclusive agreement between you and Elderfield & Hall, except as otherwise agreed in writing signed by us. Our failure to assert a right or insist upon compliance with any term or condition shall not constitute a waiver of that right or excuse any subsequent noncompliance.
EFFECTIVE DATE
These Terms and Conditions are effective as of December 1, 2010. We reserve the right to change them by posting a revision on this website.
WEBSITE USE
GRANT OF LIMITED USE LICENSE
Elderfield & Hall grants you a limited, nonexclusive, non-transferable license to access and use this website only in accordance with and for the purposes set forth in these Terms and Conditions. You do not have permission to access or use this website in any way or for any purpose that involves a violation of these Terms and Conditions.
OWNERSHIP; SCOPE OF LICENSE
This website is intended only for your use in deciding whether to purchase products from us and in purchasing products from us. You may access and make a limited number of copies of the frames or pages only as needed for this limited purpose. Any unauthorized use, change of information, or interference with the availability of, access to proper working of or security measures on this website is strictly prohibited.
OTHER USE
Unless expressly permitted by us, any copying, mirroring, archiving, intercepting or redirecting of content from any part of this website is strictly prohibited. Redistribution, making a derivative work from and any other commercial exploitation of any content you download from this website is expressly prohibited. Using bots, spiders, other indexing agents or any other device to copy any part of this website or use of any technology or other means to hide your identity when accessing this website are also strictly prohibited. You agree you will impose only that load on this website which is necessary for your use in deciding whether to purchase products from us and in purchasing products from us.
SALES TERMS
PURCHASES; PRICES; PAYMENT
Prices, title and risk of loss are F.O.B. our warehouse. Published prices don't include taxes, duties or shipping and may be changed without notice. Visa, MasterCard, and American Express are accepted for telephone, website and fax orders. Credit card arrangements are subject to change. We reserve the right to correct typographic errors and reject orders. Applicable law may prevent the sale of some products in your area.
We accept wire transfers. Call or email for details.
SALES TAX
Illinois sales tax applies to orders shipped within the State of Illinois.
DAMAGED SHIPMENTS
In the event your shipment arrives damaged it is imperative that you note the damage on the bill of lading or other shipping document. Elderfield & Hall will not be responsible for un-noted damage. In the case of concealed damage you must notify the carrier immediately and then contact Elderfield & Hall for assistance in filing your claim with the carrier.
LIMITED PRODUCT WARRANTY
All products sold by Elderfield & Hall are sourced or made from the highest quality industrial components and materials.
The new machines sold on this website are guaranteed to be free from defects in materials and workmanship for a period of one year from date of receipt at your facility, with the exception of Sharpshooter™ Tungsten Grinders which are warranted to be free from defects in materials and workmanship for a period of 5 years from date of receipt at your facility. In the event a defect is found within the warranty period, we will, at our sole discretion, provide replacement parts for your onsite use, or repair the machine when you have shipped it prepaid to us, or replace the defective machine.
Consumable products such as saw blades, tungsten electrodes and diamond wheels are warranted to be free from defects. If a question of defect arises, the item must be returned at your cost for evaluation and possible replacement.
Our only warranty obligation is to replace any item proved defective in material or workmanship. ALL OTHER WARRANTIES, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR PURPOSE, ARE DISCLAIMED.
PRODUCT INFORMATION
Information about products is subject to change without notice. SOME PRODUCTS SOLD BY US CONTAIN INGREDIENTS KNOWN TO THE STATE OF CALIFORNIA TO CAUSE CANCER AND BIRTH DEFECTS OR OTHER REPRODUCTIVE HARM. UPON REQUEST, WE WILL FURNISH YOU WITH MATERIAL SAFETY DATA SHEETS FOR HAZARDOUS SUBSTANCES AS DEFINED BY OSHA AND A LIST OF PRODUCTS OR SUBSTANCES KNOWN BY THE STATE OF CALIFORNIA TO CAUSE CANCER OR REPRODUCTIVE HARM.
GOVERNMENT PROCUREMENT
Items sold by us may not meet certain government procurement requirements (such as those imposed by the Buy American Act). Upon request, we will provide you with origin information. If you require other information or have other special needs, please contact Sales and Customer Service.
OTHER PROVISIONS
NO OTHER REPRESENTATIONS OR WARRANTIES
WE MAKE NO REPRESENTATION OR WARRANTY THAT PRODUCTS OFFERED FOR SALE ON THIS WEBSITE ARE LEGAL, AVAILABLE OR APPROPRIATE FOR YOUR PURPOSES OR FOR USE IN YOUR COUNTRY OR REGION. YOU ARE RESPONSIBLE FOR COMPLIANCE WITH LAWS GOVERNING YOUR USE OF THESE PRODUCTS. THIS WEBSITE IS PROVIDED "AS IS" WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED. YOU HAVE THE SOLE RESPONSIBILITY FOR ADEQUATE PROTECTION AND BACKUP OF DATA AND/OR EQUIPMENT USED IN CONNECTION WITH THIS WEBSITE. YOU AGREE TO HOLD ELDERFIELD & HALL HARMLESS FROM, AND YOU COVENANT NOT TO SUE ELDERFIELD & HALL FOR, ANY CLAIMS BASED ON USE OF THIS WEBSITE.
LIMITATION OF LIABILITY
UNDER NO CIRCUMSTANCES SHALL ELDERFIELD & HALL BE LIABLE IN CONTRACT, WARRANTY, TORT OR OTHERWISE FOR ANY SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, INCIDENTAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES THAT RESULT FROM YOUR PURCHASE OF ANY PRODUCTS FROM US OR ANY USE OF, OR THE INABILITY TO USE, ANY CONTENT ON THIS WEBSITE, EVEN IF WE HAVE BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES. IN NO EVENT SHALL OUR LIABILITY EXCEED THE PURCHASE PRICE OF THE PRODUCTS YOU PURCHASE FROM US.
YOUR OBLIGATIONS
You warrant, represent and agree: (1) to comply with all laws; (2) that our sale and shipment of any product ordered by you will not, by export thereof, your legal status or otherwise, cause us to violate any law; and (3) to indemnify us against any losses and costs incurred from a failure by you to comply with any law or these terms and conditions or from any unlawful use by anyone of any product ordered by you.
SECURITY
Whenever we transmit your credit card information over the Internet, we use the industry standard Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption for all pages containing private information pertaining to your shipments.
TRADEMARKS AND COPYRIGHTS
Sharpshooter™, Dual Arc 80, and Pro-Fusion (as it relates to the welding industry) are registered trademarks of Elderfield & Hall. Unless otherwise indicated, all material on this site is subject to a copyright owned by Elderfield & Hall, all rights reserved. Except as expressly permitted by us, nothing on this website confers any license in any property right, including without limitation, any right in any trademark or copyright of Elderfield & Hall or any third party.
JURISDICTION AND CHOICE OF LAW
These Terms and Conditions shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the State of Illinois applicable to contracts made and to be performed in Illinois, without giving effect to conflict of law principles, and applicable federal law. Any personal information submitted will be subject to these laws, not those of any jurisdiction outside of the United States. You irrevocably consent to the exclusive jurisdiction of the courts located in Chicago, Illinois in connection with any action arising out of or related to these Terms and Conditions or this website. Notwithstanding the foregoing, proceedings to enforce the result of any such adjudication may be brought in any applicable forum.
Call us:
865.671.7682
Fax us:
865.671.7686
E-mail us:
Sales Dept.: sales@pro-fusiononline.com
Customer Service: info@pro-fusiononline.com
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - -
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - -
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - -
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - -
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - -
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - -
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - -
Return to Top
About Pro-Fusion
Copyright © 2003-2015 Pro-Fusion by Elderfield & Hall.
